<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Country_Profile</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_text">
        Bangladesh is my Favourite country. I live in Bangladesh. Bangladesh is my Homeland.
        \n\nThey have many beautiful place. Bangladesh is a small country in the word.
        \n\nI am a student of ICE at
			Pabna university of science and technology. My  fathers name is Mohammad Ali.My
			Mothers name is Most. Sultana Raziya.I live in Bangladesh. Bangladesh is my favourite country
			because Bangladesh is my homeland and they have many beautiful place.
        \n\nWe want to bring it to the notice of the concerned authority that mosquito menace has increased in our locality. Mosquitoes breed freely
            in the dirty water of the drains and dither hr fhu tge the morning and in the focus of our country .\n\nLaptop is a electronic device. it
            is most helpful of our digital country. bendite our laptop  it can possible.

    </string>
    <string name="india_text">
        India is my Favourite country. I live in India. India is my Homeland.
        \n\nThey have many beautiful place. India is a large country in the word.
        \n\nI am a student of ICE at
			Pabna university of science and technology. My  fathers name is Mohammad Ali.My
			Mothers name is Most. Sultana Raziya.I live in India. India is my favourite country
			because India is my homeland and they have many beautiful place.
        \n\nWe want to bring it to the notice of the concerned authority that mosquito menace has increased in our locality. Mosquitoes breed freely
            in the dirty water of the drains and dither hr fhu tge the morning and in the focus of our country .\n\nLaptop is a electronic device. it
            is most helpful of our digital country. bendite our laptop  it can possible.
    </string>
     <string name="pakistan_text">
        Pakistan is my Favourite country. I live in Pakistan. Pakistan is my Homeland.
        \n\nThey have many beautiful place. Pakistan is a small country in the word.
        \n\nI am a student of ICE at
			Pabna university of science and technology. My  fathers name is Mohammad Ali.My
			Mothers name is Most. Sultana Raziya.I live in Pakistan. Pakistan is my favourite country
			because Pakistan is my homeland and they have many beautiful place.
        \n\nWe want to bring it to the notice of the concerned authority that mosquito menace has increased in our locality. Mosquitoes breed freely
            in the dirty water of the drains and dither hr fhu tge the morning and in the focus of our country .\n\nLaptop is a electronic device. it
            is most helpful of our digital country. bendite our laptop  it can possible.
    </string>

</resources>